Jensen, Vernon Papers /3002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Vernon Jensen Papers
1930-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jensen, Vernon.
/3002
38 cubic feet
38 linear ft.
Administrative papers.
Research material from ILR Professor Vernon Jensen's office files.
3070296
Biographical / Historical
Vernon Jensen (July 10, 1907 - September 27, 1998) was a founding faculty member of Cornell's New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
A graduate of Brigham Young University (BS '32), Jensen worked as a substitute teacher in Salt Lake City after college before leaving to pursue graduate study at the University of California at Berkeley (PhD '39). Shortly before completing his degree, Jensen began teaching at the University of Colorado. He taught at UC from 1937 to 1946, during which time he also served as a consultant to the National Defense Mediation Board (1941) and a public panel member, mediator and arbitrator for the National War Labor Board (1942) and Wage Stabilization Director of the NWLB's Ninth Region (1942-1944).
Jensen was among the founding faculty of the School of Industrial and Labor Relations, joining Cornell in 1946. Jensen became Associate Dean of the ILR School in 1965 and was elected to Cornell's Board of Trustees in 1973. In addition to numerous articles, Jensen wrote four books, Lumber and Labor (1945), Heritage of Conflict (1950), Collective Bargaining in the Nonferrous Metal Industry (1955), and Hiring of Dockworkers and Employment Practices in the Ports of New York, London, Liverpool, Rotterdam, and Marseilles (1964).
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor Vernon Jensen
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4007: Vernon Jensen Additional Records /4067: Vernon Jensen Longshore Research Files /4096: Vernon H. Jensen Additional Research and Office Files /4128: Vernon Jensen Additional Papers /4137: Vernon Jensen Additional Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2016
Lumber trade -- United States; Railroads--United States.; Stevedores -- United States; Jensen, Vernon H.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3070296
- Labor Journal (Everett), 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Timber Worker (Aberdeen) 1936 Federation of Food Workers (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Timber Worker (Aberdeen) 1937 Federation of Food Workers (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Timber Worker (Duluth) 1937 Federation of Food Workers (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Timber Worker (Seattle) 1938 International Woodworkers of Am. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Midwest Labor (Duluth) 1938 Midwest CIO (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Timber Worker (Seattle) 1939 International Woodworkers of Am. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Timber Worker (Seattle) 1939 International Woodworkers of Am. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Midwest Labor (Duluth) 1939 Midwest CIO (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Timber Worker (Seattle) 1940 International Woodworkers of Am. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Midwest Labor (Duluth) 1940 Midwest CIO (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Timber Worker (Seattle) 1941 International Woodworkers of Am. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Shingle Weaver (Aberdeen) 1942 Shingle Weavers Council, AFL (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Constitutions and By-Laws, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Federation of Woodworkers, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- IWA - 1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- IWA - 1937 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- IWA - 1940,1941 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Oregon State Fed. Of Labor 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Oregon State Fed. Of Labor, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Oregon-Washington Council of Lumber and Sawmill Workers, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Publications, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 4L Board of Directors, Reports of Semi-Annual Meetings, 1923/7 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 4L Board of Directors, Reports of Semi-Annual Meetings, 1928/9, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 4L Board of Directors, Reports of Semi-Annual Meeting, 1930/5, 1930-1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 4L Board of Directors, Reports of Semi-Annual Meeting, 1936/7, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 4L Committee on Constitutional Revision, Report, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 4L Communications from Locals, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 4L Constitution and By-Laws, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 4L District Conventions, Reports, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 4L Employee Wood Promotion Conference, Reports, 1928/9, 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 4L Executive Committee Meetings, Reports, 1934/5, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 4L Going Wage Tabulations 1923-1928 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 4L Going Wage Tabulations 1933-1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 4L History, Jurisdiction, and Purpose, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Ladies Loyal Legion (3L), 1930 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 4L Minimum Wage Scales and Regulations, 1921-1932 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 4L Minimum Wage Scales and Regulations, 1933-1936 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 4L Miscellaneous Publications, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 4L Overtime Regulations 1924-1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 4L Wage Board Meetings, Reports, 1934/6, 1934-1936 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 4L Bulletin and 4L Lumber News, Newsclippings, 1918-1936 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 4L Employment Service Letter 1925-1928 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- 4L News Letter - 1922 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Columbia Basin Employers Labor News Digest - 1939 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Columbia Basin Employers Labor News Digest - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Columbia Basin Employers Labor News Digest - 1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Columbia Basin Loggers - 1940 Communications and Reports (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Grays Harbor Industrial Council 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Lumber Information - 1936 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1940 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1941 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1942 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1943 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1944 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications July/Dec. - 1944 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Lumbermen's Ind. Rel. Committee Communications - 1945 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- National Lumber Manufacturers Association, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Southern Pine Associations 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Southern Pine Association 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Southern Pine Association 1921-1929 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Southern Pine Association 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Southern Pine Association 1936-1938 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Southern Pine Association 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Southern Pine Association (No Date) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Southern Pine Association - Industrial Information Service - 1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Timber Producers Association Bulletin 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- West Coast Lumbermen's Assoc. 1930-1937 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- West Coast Lumbermen's Assoc. Labor News Bulletin, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Western Operators Association (Wage Statistics) 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Western Operators Association (Wage Statistics) 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Willamette Valley Lumber Operators Association - 1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Agreements, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Arbitration by Father George Thompson - 5/22/37, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Arbitration by Vernon H. Jenson, NWLB Case 90 6/16/42, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Arbitration by Pendleton Howard, NWLB Case #69 - 7/1/42, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Negotiations 7/10/40 - 9/18/40, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Negotiations 12/5/40 - 12/10/40, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Negotiations 3/5/41 - 5/10/41, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- National Defense Mediation Board - 7/30/41, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- National Defense Mediation Board - 8/19/41 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- National Defense Mediation Board, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- National Defense Mediation Board - Jenson (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Negotiations 3/23/42 - 3/25/42, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- National Labor Relations Board Press Releases 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- National War Labor Board Booth-Kelly Case, V.H. Jenson, HO, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- National War Labor Board Lumber Case Decisions, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- National War Labor Board, WCLC Press Releases, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- National War Labor Board, OWI Press Releases, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- National War Labor Board, DPI Press Releases 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- National War Labor Board, West Coast Lumber Commission, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Wage and Hour Division Atlanta, Georgia Office, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Wage and Hour Division Press Releases - 1940 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- National Recovery Administration, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- National Resources Committee, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- National Resources Planning Board (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Department of Agriculture 1923-1928 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Department of Agriculture -1929 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Department of Agriculture 1933-1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Farm Security Administration, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Council of National Defense (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Forest Service - 1933 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Forest Service - 1933 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Forest Service 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Forest Service 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Forest Service 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Arkansas, Arkansas Forestry Commission (Box 5, Folder 6)
- California - California Code Commission, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Georgia - State Planning Board, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Minnesota - State Board of Health, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Minnesota - State Planning Board, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Oregon - Bureau of Labor, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Oregon - State Industrial Accident Commission, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Oregon - State Planning Board, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Texas - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Texas - The Texas Planning Board, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Washington - Dept. of Conservation and Development (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Washington - Dept. of Labor - Reports, 1922-1931 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Washington - Dept. of Labor - Reports, 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Washington - Dept. of Labor - Safety and Labor Laws, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Wisconsin - State Planning Board, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Colleges and University #1, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Colleges and Universities #2, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Publications 1927-1936 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Publications 1936-1939 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- National War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Report of the Steel Panel (Box 6, Folder 2)
- National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Emergency Board No. 133/ Report to the President by the 12/10/60, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission - Misc. 1/61-4/62, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Presidential Railroad Commission - Report 2/62, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- B.L.F.E. The Enginemen's press 3/2/62 "Worst Report in Railroad Labor History", 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Railroads' Exhibit #2A, 1, 2, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Railroads' Exhibit #2B, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Railroads' Exhibit #3, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Railroads' Exhibit #5, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Railroads' Exhibit #6, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Railroads' Exhibit #6A, 1953-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Railroads' Exhibit #7, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Railroads' Exhibit #8, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Railroads' Exhibit #9, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Railroads' Exhibit #10, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Railroads' Exhibit #11, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Railroads' Exhibit #12, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Railroads' Exhibit #13, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol 2., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 3, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 4, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 6, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 7, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 8, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission Transcript of Proceedings Vol. 9, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- The New York Times 5/4/62 Clippings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission - Report (Drafts of May 4-14,1962) (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Railroad Marine Workers Commission - Report. 6/62, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Railroad Light Captains Commission - Report 7/62, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Publications 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Periodical Articles, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Bibliographical Data, 1939-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Court Materials, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Glossary of Lumber Industry Terminology (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  3 Photographs
- Interview - E.Z. Nichols New Orleans, La. 12/28/40, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Jenson Correspondence 1936-1939 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Jenson Correspondence 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Jenson Correspondence 1941 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Jenson Correspondence January/May - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Jenson Correspondence June/December - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Jenson Correspondence 1943-1945 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 1st through 7th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 8th through 14th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct 15th through 21st, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 22nd through 28th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Oct. 29th through Nov. 4th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 5th through 11th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 12th through 18th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 19th through 25th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Nov. 26th through Dec. 2nd, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 3rd through 9th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 10th through 16th, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 17th through 23rd, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Dec. 24th through 30th, and 31st, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Industrial Relations Seminar, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Waterfront Commission of N.Y. Harbor Daily Activity Report, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 1st through 2nd, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Waterfront Commission of New York Harbor, Daily Activity Reports: Apr. 3rd through 9th, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 2)